So, as to continue the video,
I'm going to show you or demonstrate you how the,
uh, video made, was made.
So, here I have a, Here's the prompt here that we're going to
use to make the picture and ads,
I mean the scene. So first,
we're going to copy.
So, as you can see, we have already a picture here that
we're going to use to make the video or scene.
So, we're going to,
Paste it here and paste the prompt here
along with the
I'm just making sure that it is number one so it
will generate one video at a time.
So we're just going to wait and see the results.
So, the video was finished. Let's watch it again.
So, this was perfect. So,
we're going to make the video. Rest, copy the voice
over, ay, no I mean copy the prompt first to
make the picture.
💕
And we're going to paste it here so it will have a
preference. We're
going to do the rest also.
Copy it, paste it here,
paste the picture here. Click the clip,
Manang Preference.
So this was faster. Compared to
making it one by one.
And then you'll choose what pictures you're going to
use. So,
I'll just use, Here is
this one. Oh wait.
Here and here. And use.
Yeah. Oh,
I forgot to run.
And we're going to do the same to
make the video.